Hi, 
Thank you for purchase,
I hope, my package will help you,

For the test, at first please add the layers (Ball, Canvas, Wall, MainBall, Graund, GUI)
and add the scenes  ("GameStart" , "Game" and Loader)  in the File/Build Settings
as shown in the image  "Assets/BallPool/TagAndLayers.png"

and  open the scene "Assets/BallPool/Scenes/GameStart" and click play :) ,


In the script "MasterServerGUI"
you can use type of your "Network" (UNITY_NETWORK, PHOTON_NETWORK or other)
you can change this in the menu - File/Build Settings/Player Settings/ Other Settings/Configuration/Scripting Define Symbols
You can also not use Network…

In the script "ServerController" you can change the attribute "SomeRPC" for your Networking …

In the scene "Assets/BallPool/Scenes/GameStart" you can find a GameObject "ControllerGenerator",
It creates an object of prefab "MenuController" which then passes to other scenes and controls the game.


In the scene "Assets/BallPool/Scenes/Game" you can find a GameObject "CueController",

GameObject  "CueController" is controlled by Script "CueController",

Open this Script and see the parameters in the #region Parameters

1) ballsDistance - this is a distance of balls in the start, (correctly when it is a zero),
2) cueMaxDisplacement - this is a maximum displacement of the cue during shot,
3) ballMaxVelocity - this is a maximum velocity of the ball during shot, with maximum displacement of the cue,
4) ballLineLength - this is a maximum length of the line, which shows the direction of the velocity after hitting balls,
5) ballAngularVelocityCurve - defines the angular velocity of the ball at impact, 
depending on the impact force,
6) ballVelocityCurve - when the ball collides with another ball, he loses the linear velocity,
but, because it also has a angular velocity, he can ride forward after collision
depending on the increased the force shot , the  ball gets a less angular velocity because no time to roll on the ground,
7) touchSensitivityCurve - this is a control  sensitivity of cue for the mobile devices.


In the Prefab "Assets/BallPool/Game/Prefabs/Ball" you can find a Prefab  "Ball",

Prefab  "Ball" has a Script "BallController",

It has properties ("isMain", "isBlack", "ballType" ) that are defined in the script "CueController" during their creation,
Also It has properties ("moveSmoothSpline" and "moveSmooth" ) which determine  the damping ball speed, and has properties ("moveSendSmoothSpline" and "moveSendSmooth") which determine the damping ball speed for sending from network.

The Script "MasterServerGUI" creates and manages the server, 
The Script "ServerController" together with  Script  "ServerMessenger" manages the network messaging.
For the use other multiplayer, only need to change body of the function  "SendRPCToNetworkView" , "SendRPCToNetworkPlayer" 
in the Script "ServerController" and change  the Attribute  [RPC].
The logic of the game, manages the script "GameManager",  It has a field "myProfile" and otherProfile,
The script "Profile" describes a profile for players,

In the scene "Assets/BallPool/Scenes/Game" you can find a GameObject "TargetsAI",
This Gameobject has childs "Target" points, in which aims the AI ​​.

Good luck!


